papersizes.io 2019-03-31

# Paper Sizes | Privacy

##### Privacy & Cookie Policy

This privacy policy sets out how PaperSizes uses and protects any information that you give PaperSizes when you use this website.

PaperSizes is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

PaperSizes may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

_

What we collect  
We may collect the following information:

  * Contact information including email address and phone number
  * Other information relevant to client feedback forms

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service.

Any information that you send directly to us via email or the forms is treated as completely confidential and is never ever passed on to a third party without your express permission.

_

Security  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

_

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit 'How to delete and control cookies' for detailed guidance.

The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an 'implied consent' policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser's anonymous usage setting (called 'Incognito' in Chrome, 'InPrivate' for Internet Explorer, 'Private Browsing' in Firefox and Safari etc). This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

_

First Party Cookies  
These are cookies that are set by this website directly. We use cookies to remember your choice of background colour for the website, and your dimension choice (mm, cm, m or inches, etc).

_

Google Analytics  
We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.

You can find out more about Google's position on privacy as regards its analytics service at [Safeguarding Your Google Analytics Data'](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245).

_

Hotjar  
We use [Hotjar](http://www.hotjar.com/) in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on [this link](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).

You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this [opt-out](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out) link.

_

Third Party Cookies  
These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by Twitter and Facebook. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.

You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.

_

Links to other websites  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

_

This website and its content is copyright of PaperSizes - © PaperSizes 2018. All rights reserved.

Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:

  * You may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only
  * You may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material
  * You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.

_

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by PaperSizes and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website. Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of PaperSizes. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, PaperSizes takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
